baianat.com 2016-04-07

# Privacy Policy

Last modified : 04 Oct 2015

If you send your personal information to us, it means you that have read and agreed to the purposes set out in this policy. 

We are fully committed to protecting your privacy. 

Baianat company did not share or sell your personal information not now nor in the future to other institutions or companies for the purpose of promotion or any other purposes. 

In the case of a service request or attempt to contact us we will need some of your contact information such as phone number, e­mail or your address so we can contact you and respond to your request or complete the requested service. 

We did not provide this information to a third party definitively without your permission, except if it is required to complete the application process. 

Baianat company may at any time review the privacy policy by updating this post. So, you are bound by any such modifications, and should therefore always visit this page to to check the latest copy of the Privacy Policy. 

Could also inform you about updates that are performed on this policy through our call center staff. 

When we get your personal information, we take all necessary measures to protect it from unauthorized access or disclosure, and we don’t allow any mistakes to happen while sending your data to us, nor passed to any third party. 

All e-mail messages and faxes going between us and the customer are reserved in private records that are protected so that we can help you quickly and easily when you want another more requests at another time, and also to measure and improve our customer service. 

The company reserves your personal information only during the period in which it considers necessary to achieve specific purposes, unless the law permits or request a longer period to keep them. 

At the end of the period of information reservation, or earlier if you ask us not to keep your personal information. 

Baianat website may contain external links to other websites. Please be aware that we are not responsible for these other websites agreements. In case signed out of our website, we are not responsible if you send your personal information or use it in any website. 

Children are not eligible to use our services, we ask who is under the age of 18 not to send any personal information or use our services.
